tinglebytes.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | TingleBytes

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Tinglebytes collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the <http://tinglebytes.com/> website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Tinglebytes.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identifying information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. The user’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for recordkeeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. The user may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

Tinglebytes may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _\- To improve customer service_  
The information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
  * _\- To personalize  the user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _\- To improve our Site_  
We may use the feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * _\- To send periodic emails_  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identifiable information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identifying information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Tinglebytes has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  

This document was last updated on December 05, 2013

### [Raghuvarya Chowdary](http://tinglebytes.com/author/raghuvarya/ "Raghuvarya Chowdary")

Hi, Am Raghuvarya from Hyderabad, India. Am an Undergrad Student from computer science student. I grabbed my interest on blogging through my friend and started TingleBytes. Am passionate about gadgets and very much interested in reviewing them. You can get in touch with me through my Social Profiles Facebook and Google+. Or Contact me via eMail : raghuvarya@tinglebytes.com. Thank You For Your Support :) Keep Visiting Us :)

[More Posts](http://tinglebytes.com/author/raghuvarya/ "More posts by Raghuvarya Chowdary") \- [Website](http://tinglebytes.com/ "Raghuvarya Chowdary")

Follow Me:
